Alright, so now in this video we're going to go ahead and add flash light to the player.
Alright, so for adding the flash light in the third precision controller prefab the
items then in the items if you click on this journal in here we have this flash light
okay and also if you open up the FPS character I mean click on it click on inventory
and then in here we have this flash light as well, alright and then in this flash light
we have this spotlight if you turn it on click on scene view let's double click on this
spotlight okay and make sure that you are in the shared it and drum would okay if
you are in that mood then you will be able to see lights okay and all of the effects as
well so in the flash light if you turn on the spotlight like that as you can see the
spotlight turns on right there okay so we need the spotlight so what I'm going to do
I'm going to duplicate it and then I'm going to move this outside okay so I'm just going
to put it right down below the player related now let's turn everything I mean minimize
everything and then let's open up the camera and in the camera let's try and drop this
light and then turn it on again and then you can click on reset and when you click on
reset now the light is in front as you can see click on game view we are okay now we need
to fix this so where is it there is the light let's move it down below let me reset it
again and then move it down so that we can see it all happening I think this will be a good
value for it all right for the light we need to change its spot angle 255 all right and also
we need to make it a bit yellow all righty not just what just a bit light yellow all right like that
intensity is good and everything else as well all right when you fix it in this position then you
can go ahead and play the game and test it out all right when we play the game now as you can see
the light is somewhere right there which is not good all right so now we will check it out here we are
let's select the light as you can see the light is now in front of it so now we need to move it back
okay like behind the player all right let's actually go ahead and pick up the gun so that we
know how the player hold the gun and then we will fix it up all right for now it looks good
okay if you now hold this gun all right here we are now let's go ahead and fix it it looks
good like this as well but if you unlock the cursor click on scene we know let's double click on
the spot light here it is let's move it up a bit let's click on scene now I think it looks good
okay so make sure that you make the spot light in the same position as this okay in the
player doesn't get on these stairs we will fix it collider don't worry but now as you can see
spot light I mean the flashlight or you can call it the spot light it looks good we can see everything
in the environment with it and now before stopping the game you will have to copy its component
the transform of this spotlight okay I will copy two times just to be sure then select this
spotlight again and then click on paste component values that is all you have to do
then let's click on scene view let's check these stairs all right these stairs have
let's remove convex from these and let's now go ahead and play the game again
all right the flashlight is good all right you can choose this flashlight which is always
thrown on or you can use the other flashlight which the player have okay but I prefer this one
because if the player is holding that flashlight in the hand then how will the player be able to
shoot zombies okay because the player can't hold flashlight and gun in both hands okay so that's
why the flashlight is automatic and then the player can hold gun like this as you can see
in the environment okay so everything is perfect now which is gonna end this right here